{
    "id": "3aafb855af1c42feadd4acb1b09ebaef",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. cooked dinner.",
            "description": "We use emphatic pronouns for emphasis.",
            "answers": [
                "herself",
                "herselves"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a0ca3b2540d467ba040fda9bb8f619e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I injured ………………………… while playing.",
            "description": "The reflexive pronoun is used when the subject and object refer to the same person or thing.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "96a3b8dd5b604b15a7470bd2d051e7fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… of these arguments is valid.",
            "description": "Both should be followed by a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "82c00a43e9164c06bf7a311d9f27f64f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl lost a ring ………………………….. was made of gold.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses both which and that can refer to things.",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5299a43158734b409cba6dc9492e8e02"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is my friend ……………………….. you met yesterday.",
            "description": "Who is possible here in an informal style. ",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "which",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b77c5f363b941c08e03cb5ecf35fc8b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tiger …………………………. was captured last month is now kept in a zoo.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses both that and which can refer to animals.",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ed0e0a6fd7bf453c882f6d87e1cadd18"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw a man ………………………….. had lost his arms.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "edfa601ad3ee4738b076bbbc74d57e4d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Abraham Lincoln was the best President ………………………… ever ruled America.",
            "description": "In identifying relative clauses, both who and that can refer to people. ",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "06b3c852aef5454282a4551a2ec57b1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ………………………… they caught was a thief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d68f109805f64c04bfaf04b7f9e9ec7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw a girl …………………………. eyes were green.",
            "description": "Whose is a possessive relative pronoun. It can replace words like her, his etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "who's",
                "whose",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca6705f9d9cc4eeaa545dd3c343316e1"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. of these methods work.",
            "description": "Both is followed by a plural verb.",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a55621c0fc85413fa12f0cc3be38e2da"
        }
    ]
}